www.beast.run
www.beast.run
[Music]
[音樂]
Imagine having just one lightweight backpack that's good for anything,
想像你只擁有一個輕量化背包，卻能應付所有冒險，
from short day hikes to long mountain trips or even family outings.
無論是短程的一日健行、長途高山旅行，甚至家庭出遊。
This is the Tornado Vest Pack by Hanchor and Beast Runners.
這就是由 Hanchor 和跑山獸攜手打造的 TORNADO 疾行登山背心背包。
Let's see if it's the all-in-one solution for every adventure.
讓我們來看看它是否能成為應付所有冒險的萬用解決方案。
Hi, I'm Petr from Beast Runners 跑山獸.
大家好，我是來自跑山獸的 Petr。
Today I am reviewing the TORNADO Vest Pack
今天我將為大家介紹 TORNADO 疾行登山背心背包，
after testing it in Taiwan's mountains.
這是我在台灣山區長期測試後的心得分享。
We team up with Hanchor, a popular backpack maker from Taiwan,
我們與台灣知名背包品牌 Hanchor 合作，
to create Tornado Vest Pack.
共同設計了 TORNADO 疾行登山背心背包。
We made these partnership
之所以促成這次合作，
because mountain activities have become really popular in Taiwan.
是因為登山活動在台灣變得非常盛行。
As trail runners, we often have problems with backpacks
身為越野跑者，我們常遇到一個問題，
that were too small or lack safety features for longer trips.
背包的容量太小，或缺乏長途行程所需的安全機能。
The Tornado Vest Pack solves this by offering a 32-Liter capacity
Tornado疾行登山背心背包 解決了這個問題，它提供 32 公升的容量，
while still being comfortable and easy to move with.
同時保有舒適度和良好的行動性。
The Tornado Vest Pack is made for both hikers and trail runners.
這款 疾行登山背心背包 是專為登山者與越野跑者設計的。
It gives you more safety and enough space for your gear
它能為你在困難的長途登山旅程中，
on long difficult trips in the mountains.
提供更高的安全性和足夠的裝備收納空間。
This pack is for people who want to move light and fast,
這個背包是為了那些希望輕裝快速移動，
but still be prepared for anything the mountain can throw at them.
但仍能為山林中可能遇到的任何狀況做好準備的人而設計。
It's about having one pack you can
它的核心理念是，讓你擁有一款背包，
trust for many different kinds of trips.
就能信賴它應付各種不同的旅程。
It's great for anyone who enjoys exploring mountains safely and comfortably.
它非常適合任何喜歡安全、舒適地探索山林的人。
In mountains, picking the right gear is key for safety.
在山裡，選擇合適的裝備是確保安全的關鍵。
The 32-liter size helps you pack smart,
32 公升的容量能幫助你精簡打包，
carrying only essential, lightweight items
只攜帶必要的輕量化物品，
without sacrificing safety.
同時不犧牲安全性。
Packing lighter means you can move easier,
打包得越輕，你的行動就越輕鬆，
feel less tired, and enjoy your time in the mountains more.
疲勞感越低，也更能享受在山裡的美好時光。
This pack is perfect size to carrying everything you need
這個背包的尺寸恰到好處，能裝下所有你需要的東西，
and nothing you don't.
不多也不少。
A great thing about this pack
這款背包最棒的一點是，
is how easy it adjusts for different trip lengths.
它可以輕鬆調整以適應不同長度的旅程。
Whether you are heading out for a one-day hike
無論你是一日健行，
or a five-day adventure,
還是五天探險，
you can compress it down for light load or expand it to carry more.
你可以將它壓縮以應付輕量化需求，或擴展以攜帶更多東西。
The rolltop closure lets you size it from 32-liters down to 14,
捲收式開口讓容量能從 32 公升壓縮到 14 公升，
keeping your gear packed tight and secure
無論你攜帶多少東西，
no matter how much you are carrying.
都能保持裝備穩固又安全。
So if you start a trip with a lot of food,
所以如果你一開始攜帶了很多食物，
the pack gets more and more stable as you eat it.
隨著你吃掉它們，背包會變得越來越穩定。
It's always the right size for what you are carrying.
它總是能符合你當下攜帶的物品量。
To keep it super compact and secure,
為了讓它變得更緊實、更牢固，
you can properly buckle the rolltop down to the side of the pack.
你可以將捲收式開口妥善地扣到背包兩側。
But for those quick, convenient moments,
但如果你需要快速方便的取物，
there is also what I call "lazy way".
我也有一種我稱為「懶人式」的收納方式。
You can simply connect the buckle to each other over the top,
你可以直接將扣具在頂部互相扣住，
even when you are wearing the vest for quick closure.
即使你正背著背包也能快速閉合。
This is super handy when I am constantly pulling out jackets
這在我與女兒的家庭旅行中非常實用，
or snacks for my daughters during a family trip.
尤其是當我需要不斷地拿出外套或零食時。
The mountains in Taiwan can be very tough
台灣山區的環境可能非常嚴峻，
so being safe and comfortable is very important,
所以確保安全與舒適非常重要，
especially on longer trips.
尤其是在長途旅程中。
The Tornado Vest Pack has enough room without limiting your movement
TORNADO 疾行登山背心背包在不限制你活動的情況下提供了足夠的空間，
keeping you comfortable, even on rough trails.
即使在崎嶇不平的步道上，也能讓你感到舒適。
After all, who likes to carry a heavy bouncy backpack?
畢竟，誰喜歡背著一個沉重又容易晃動的背包呢？
This vest fits close to your body,
這款背心能緊貼你的身體，
so it feels more likea piece of clothing than a big, heavy bag.
讓你感覺它更像一件衣服，而不是一個笨重的背包。
The Tornado Vest Pack uses strong 100D ripstop fabric, light but very durable.
TORNADO 疾行登山背心背包使用堅固的 100D 抗撕裂面料，輕巧但非常耐用。
The ripstop fabric stops smaller tears from growing bigger,
抗撕裂面料能防止小裂痕擴大
adding durability without extra weight.
在不增加重量的情況下提升了耐用性。
It also has a polycarbonate coating, which is tougher than standard coatings.
它還有一層聚碳酸酯塗層，比一般塗層更堅韌。
It's strong waterproof up to 2000mm
它具有高達 2000mm 的強力防水性能，
and resists UV damage and wear from rubbing.
並能抵抗紫外線和磨損。
I always recommend using waterproof liners or dry bags inside the pack.
但我仍然建議在背包內使用防水內袋或壓縮袋。
The weather can be really unforgiving.
山裡的天氣總是難以預測。
And under mechanical load, no fabric is perfectly waterproof.
在機械壓力下，沒有任何面料能做到完全防水。
Your main goal should always be to keep
你的主要目標永遠是確保你的睡袋
your sleeping bag and warm clothing dry.
和保暖衣物保持乾燥。
It is frameless pack.
這是一個無框架背包。
There is no heavy frame, keeping the Vest Pack very light.
沒有笨重的骨架，讓這款疾行登山背心背包非常輕。
But here is the clever part.
但巧妙之處就在這裡。
We have included a special compartment
我們在背包背面設計了一個專用隔層，
on the backside of the pack for 4-segment Mpad,
可以放入隨附的四折 Mpad 背板，
which comes included.
它能增加背負支撐性。
You can easily insert it for more support and weight distribution,
你可以輕鬆將它插入，以獲得更好的支撐和重量分配，
and you can also attach a simple hip belt for even better stability.
也可以搭配一個簡單的腰帶來獲得更好的穩定性。
This is great, because you can choose.
這非常棒，因為你可以自由地選擇。
If you won't go super light, you don't need the pad.
如果你想超輕量化，就不需要背板。
If you have a heavier load,
如果你的負重較重，
put the pad in for extra comfort and protection to your back.
就裝上背板，為你的背部提供額外的舒適和保護。
It's all about adapting the pack to your adventure.
一切都為了讓背包能夠適應你的冒險。
There are three big meshpockets on the outside for more space.
背包外部有三個大網眼口袋，提供更多收納空間。
The big pocket in front is great for drying wet things,
前面的大口袋非常適合用來晾乾濕掉的東西，
like rain jacket or wet socks.
比如雨衣或濕襪子。
The pockets on the sides are easy to reach without taking the pack off.
兩側的口袋在不卸下背包的情況下依然很容易取用。
There is also a pocket on the bottom,
底部還有一個口袋，
perfect for things you use a lot during a hike.
非常適合存放你在健行過程中經常用到的物品。
The chest straps are elastic,
胸前綁帶是彈性的，
so they are comfortable and keeping the pack stable.
讓你在感到舒適的同時，保持背包的穩定。
Here in the front, you have pockets for two soft flasks.
胸前有兩個口袋可以放置軟式水壺。
There are also special pockets which can carry your phone or action camera.
還有專門的口袋可以攜帶手機或運動相機。
It has a waterproof layer inside, to shield your phone from your sweat.
內部設有防水層，能隔絕汗水，保護你的手機。
It's a small detail that makes a big difference,
這是一個能帶來巨大改變的小細節，
preventing that annoying lens moisture
防止你在快速拿出手機拍照時，
you often get when pulling your phone out for a quick photo.
鏡頭因為汗氣而起霧。
The Vest Pack come with our 700ml soft Beast flask.
這款疾行登山背心背包附贈我們 700 毫升的跑山獸軟水壺。
It's perfect for drinking on the trail
它非常適合在旅途中飲用，
and it fits exactly in the front pockets.
而且剛好能放進胸前的口袋。
It holds a good amount of water for when you are on the move.
它能讓你邊移動邊補充充足的水分。
Safety is the most important thing.
安全是最重要的事。
That's why there is a special pocket on the shoulder
這就是為什麼我們在肩膀上設計了一個專門的口袋，
for an emergency satellite device like Garmin inReach.
用來放置緊急衛星通訊裝置，如 Garmin inReach。
It's always in place where you can reach it fast
它隨時都在你能快速可取得的地方，
in emergency every second counts.
在緊急時刻，每一秒都至關重要。
You can't waste time digging for your satellite messenger,
你不能浪費時間翻找你的衛星通訊裝置，
plus it needs a clear view of the sky to get a signal.
而且它需要清晰的天空視野才能接收信號。
This pocket keeps it in perfect spot,
這個口袋將它完美地固定在一個位置，
easy to reach and ready to connect.
易於取用，隨時準備連線。
Moving to the back, we have the rear zipper pocket
接下來看到背包後側，我們有一個後拉鍊口袋，
featuring a YKK water-resistant zipper.
採用 YKK 防水拉鍊。
This is my secure zone for items
這裡是我用來安全存放
which I don't need to access frequently during the day,
在白天不需要頻繁取用的物品的地方，
but I like keep them separately from the main chamber.
但我又想把它們和主袋分開存放。
I typically store my headlamp here after sunrise
通常日出之後，我會把頭燈放在這裡，
or spare action camera batteries during a hike.
或在健行時放備用的運動相機電池。
It is also fine for keeping some cash
它也很適合用來放一些現金，
or small items protected during family trips.
或在家庭旅行時保護小物品。
Inside there is a mesh pocket.
在背包內部，有一個網狀口袋。
You can use it to hold a waterblader
你可以用它來固定水袋，
or you can use it for small electronics
也可以用來放置小型電子產品，
like a laptop or a tablet.
例如筆電或平板電腦。
This makes pack useful not just for the trail
這讓背包不只適合戶外活動，
but also for commuting or traveling.
也適合通勤或旅行使用。
The pack comes in a few sizes.
這款背包有幾種尺寸。
Small is often good for women and medium for men.
S 號通常適合女性，M 號則適合男性。
Recently, Hanchor also made a large size for bigger guys.
最近，Hanchor 也推出了 L 號，為體型較大的男生設計。
The total weight of the west pack with Mpad is about 650 grams.
這款疾行登山背心背包連同背板的總重量約為 650 克。
The pack itself is only 500 grams.
背包本身只有 500 克。
That is very light for a pack that can do so much.
對於一款能應付這麼多功能的背包來說，這非常輕巧。
Go solo or tough terrain
如果你要獨自一人挑戰崎嶇地形，
then taking helmet is a good idea for your safety.
戴上安全帽是個不錯的主意。
You can also get the optional strap with a carabiner and hook in our e-shop
你也可以在我們的網路商店購買選配的織帶，
and use it to attach your helmet to the pack.
用它將安全帽固定在背包上。
This is perfect if you are climbing or doing anything where you need a helmet.
如果你需要攀爬或進行任何需要安全帽的活動，這會非常方便。
It keeps your helmet secure on the outside of the pack
它能將安全帽牢固地固定在背包外部，
so it doesn't take up space inside and easy to grab when you need it.
這樣就不會佔用內部空間，並且在需要時隨手可得。
In conclusion, the Tornado Vest Pack by Hanchor and Beast Runners
總結來說，由 Hanchor 和跑山獸攜手打造的 TORNADO 疾行登山背心背包，
is versatile, safe and comfortable.
是一款多功能、安全又舒適的背包。
If it looks good for your next adventure,
如果它正適合你的下一個冒險，
click the link in the description to learn more.
請點擊說明欄中的連結了解更多資訊。
Whether it's a short or a long hike or just a family trip
無論是短程、長程健行，還是家庭旅行，
this Vest Pack keeps up with you.
這款疾行登山背心背包都能與你一同前行。
Be safe out there!
祝大家在戶外平安！